Register of the Ronald I. McKinnon papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Writings by Others, 1952-2012
  - Chon, Yoo Je
    - 1984-1998 (Box-folder 16: 6)
    - 2002 (Box-folder 16: 7)
  - Chow, Gregory C., 2005 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Claassen, Emil-Maria, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Cukierman, Aleax (Box-folder 17: 2)
    - 1995-1999 (Box-folder 17: 3)
    - 2000-2002 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Clark, Gregory, 1995 June (Box-folder 17: 5)
  - Cline, William R., 2005 December (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Cooper, Richard N., 1982-1984 (Box-folder 17: 7)
  - Corbo, Vittorio, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Corden, W. Max
    - 1978-1990 (Box-folder 17: 9)
    - 2006-2009 (Box-folder 17: 10)
    - 2009-2010 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Coxhead, Ian, 2004 November (Box-folder 17: 12)
  - Cuddington, John T., 1983-1986 (Box-folder 17: 13)
  - Dasgupta, Sharmi, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - David, Paul A.
    - 1961-1973 (Box-folder 18: 2)
    - 1977-2008 (Box-folder 18: 3)
  - Davis, Donald R., 1997-2002 (Box-folder 18: 4)
  - De Cecco, Marcello, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 18: 5)
  - De Grauwe, Paul, 1984 (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - De Long, J. Bradford, 1995 (Box-folder 18: 7)
  - Demirgüç-Kunt, Ash, 2000 June (Box-folder 18: 8)
  - Desmet, Klaus, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 18: 9)
  - Devereux, Michael B., 2004 January (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Dewatripont, Mathias, 1994 March 11 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Dickinson, David G., 1994-2001 (Box-folder 19: 3)
  - Dmitriev, Kirill, 1996 (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Dooley, Michael P., 1999 December 17 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Dornbusch, Rudiger, 1971-1986 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Duffie, Darrell, 2010 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Duncan, Rod, 1998 September 16 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Easterly, William, 1993-2004 (Box-folder 19: 9)
  - Edwards, Sebastian, 1984-1993 (Box-folder 19: 10)
  - Eggerston, Thrainn, 2005 (Box-folder 20: 1)
  - Eichengreen, Barry
    - 1979-1995 (Box-folder 19: 2)
    - 1996-1999 (Box-folder 20: 3)
    - 2000-2004 (Box-folder 20: 4)
  - Emran, M. Shahe, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 20: 5)
  - Engel, Charles, 1996 (Box-folder 20: 6)
  - Erceg, Christopher J., 2005 January (Box-folder 20: 7)
  - Ergin, Evren, 1998 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Fafchamps, Marcel, 2004 (Box-folder 20: 9)
  - Faig, Miquel, 1987 (Box-folder 20: 10)
  - Faizullah-Kahn, Misrab, 2012 (Box-folder 20: 11)
  - Fan, Gang, 2006 April (Box-folder 20: 12)
  - Fischer, Stanley, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 20: 13)
  - Fitzgerald, Doireann, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Flandreau, Marc, 2003 (Box-folder 21: 1)
  - Forsyth, Tim, 2004 (Box-folder 21: 2)
  - Frankel, Jeffrey A.
    - 1992-1996 (Box-folder 21: 3)
    - 1999-2004 (Box-folder 21: 4)
    - 2007 (Box-folder 21: 5)
  - Freitag, Stephen Albert, 2011 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Frenkel, Jacob A.
    - 1971-1977 (Box-folder 21: 7)
    - 1980-1986 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1962-1989 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Froot, Kenneth A., 1987 (Box-folder 21: 10)
  - Fujita, Seiichi, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 21: 11)
  - Fukao, Mitsuhiro, 2011 (Box-folder 21: 12)
  - Fukuda, Shin-Ichi, 1994 (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - Funke, Michael, 2005 (Box-folder 22: 2)
  - Funke, Norbert, 1993 (Box-folder 22: 3)
  - Gagnon, Joseph E., 1996 (Box-folder 22: 4)
  - Galay, Karma, 2002 (Box-folder 22: 5)
  - Galbis, Vicente, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Galetovic, Alexander, 1994 (Box-folder 22: 7)
  - Gang, Zhang, 1994 March (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - Garber, Peter M., 1991-2003 (Box-folder 22: 9)
  - Garcia, Márcio, 1995-2005 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Genberg, Hans, 1974-1984 (Box-folder 22: 11)
  - Gerlach, Stefan, 2004 (Box-folder 22: 12)
  - Gilfedder, Neil J., 1995 (Box-folder 22: 13)
  - Giovanni, Alberto, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 22: 14)
  - Glodek, Sean, 1996 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Goh, Chun Kee Adrian, 2000 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - Goldstein, Henry N., 1982-1983 (Box-folder 23: 3)
  - Goodheart, Charles, 1997-2004 (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - Gordon, Robert J., 1990 (Box-folder 23: 5)
  - Goyal, Rishi, 2001 (Box-folder 23: 6)
  - Gabrisch, Hubert, 1998 (Box-folder 23: 7)
  - Gray, Roger W., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - Greenaway, David, 1993 (Box-folder 23: 9)
  - Grigg, Dana J., 1992 June 4 (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - Gross, Daniel, 2013 March 27 (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - Grossman, Gregory, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Grubel, Herbert, 2002 (Box-folder 23: 13)
  - Gruben, William C., 1999 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Hale, David D., 1994 (Box-folder 24: 2)
  - Hammam, Tarek, 2005 (Box-folder 24: 3)
  - Hammond, Peter J., 1991 (Box-folder 24: 4)
  - Hanke, Steve H., 2002-2003 (Box-folder 24: 5)
  - Harberger, Arnold C., 1980-1994 (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - Harris, Richard G., 1993 (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Hellman, Thomas, 1995 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - Henry, Peter Blair
    - 2000-2004 (Box-folder 24: 9)
    - 2006-2007 (Box-folder 24: 10)
  - Herz, Bernhard, 2002 (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Hirshleifer, Jack, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 24: 12)
  - Ho, Wei Jiang, 2003 (Box-folder 24: 13)
  - Hodder, James E., 1982-1985 (Box-folder 24: 14)
  - Hu, Xiaobu, 2005 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Hufbauer, Gary, 1995 (Box-folder 25: 2)
  - Huizinga, Harry, 1999 (Box-folder 25: 3)
  - Hussman, John P., 1990-1992 (Box-folder 25: 4)
  - Hutchinson, Michael, 2001 (Box-folder 25: 5)
  - Inman, Robert P., 2000 (Box-folder 25: 6)
  - Ito, Takatoshi, 1998 September (Box-folder 25: 7)
  - Iwasaki, Yoshihiro, 1983 May 8 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Jaensubhakij, Pichet, 1993 March (Box-folder 25: 9)
  - Jahjah, Samir, 2002 (Box-folder 25: 10)
  - Jayaratnam, Ashwini, 2003 May 12 (Box-folder 25: 11)
  - Jeanne, Olivier, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 25: 12)
  - Johnson, Harry G., 1965-1970 (Box-folder 25: 13)
  - Johnston, Bruce, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 25: 14)
  - Jones, Ronald W., 1966-2000 (Box-folder 25: 15)
  - Judd, Kenneth L., 2006 May 31 (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Kalckreuth, Ulf von, 2005 June (Box-folder 26: 2)
  - Kannan, Prakash, 2005 October (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Kant, Chander, 2003 (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - Kaplan, Ethan, 2000 (Box-folder 26: 5)
  - Kapstein, Ethan B., 1991 (Box-folder 26: 6)
  - Kapur, Basant K.
    - 1981-1990 (Box-folder 26: 7)
    - 1991-2000 (Box-folder 26: 8)
  - Kaufman, George S., 1997-2000 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - Kawai, Masahiro, 1986-2002 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Kemmerer, Donald L., 1993 (Box-folder 26: 11)
  - Kenan, Peter B., 2001-2002 (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Kim, Yoonbai, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 27: 2)
  - Kindleberger, Charles B., 1981 (Box-folder 27: 3)
  - Kingston, Christopher, 2000 November (Box-folder 27: 4)
  - Klein, L. R., 2002 April 15 (Box-folder 27: 5)
  - Koh, John, 2003 June 3 (Box-folder 27: 6)
  - Komiya, Ryutaro, 1967-1990 (Box-folder 27: 7)
  - Kornai, János, 1997 (Box-folder 27: 8)
  - Kotlikoff, Laurence J., 1993-1999 (Box-folder 27: 9)
  - Krueger, Anne, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 27: 10)
  - Krugman, Paul, 1994 November/December (Box-folder 27: 11)
  - Kuijs, Louis, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 27: 12)
  - Kumakura, Masanaga, 2004 April 30 (Box-folder 27: 13)
  - Kumhof, Michael, 2000 (Box-folder 27: 14)
  - Kugler, Maurice, 1999 (Box-folder 27: 15)
  - Kuran, Timur, 2003 January 21 (Box-folder 27: 16)
  - Kwan, Chi Hung
    - 1998 (Box-folder 28: 1)
    - 2000 June (Box-folder 28: 2)
    - 2001-2003 (Box-folder 28: 3)
  - Laffer, Arthur B., 1986 (Box-folder 28: 4)
  - Laidler, David, 1989 (Box-folder 28: 5)
  - Lalonde, Jean, 1983 (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - Lane, Timothy D., 1993 March (Box-folder 28: 7)
  - Lau, Lawrence J.
    - 1989-1991 (Box-folder 28: 8)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 28: 9)
    - 2000-2004 (Box-folder 28: 10)
  - Lane, Philip K., 2004 November (Box-folder 28: 11)
  - Läufer, Nikolaus K. A., 1992-1995 (Box-folder 28: 12)
  - Laumas, Prem S., 1986 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Lee, Brian Byongju, 2011 (Box-folder 29: 2)
  - Lee, Jeong Joon, 1995 (Box-folder 29: 3)
  - Lee, Yang-Pal, 1979 (Box-folder 29: 4)
  - Leff, Nathaniel H., 1993 (Box-folder 29: 5)
  - Leijonhufvod, Axel, 1962-2002 (Box-folder 29: 6)
  - Levich, Richard M., 1995 (Box-folder 29: 7)
  - Leland, Hayne E., 1987-1990 (Box-folder 29: 8)
  - Levine, Ross
    - 1993-1999 (Box-folder 29: 9)
    - 2000-2001 (Box-folder 29: 10)
  - Li, Hongbin, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 30: 1)
  - Li, Nan, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 30: 2)
  - Li, Xiaowei, 2003 March (Box-folder 30: 3)
  - Lindbeck, Assar, 1994-2003 (Box-folder 30: 4)
  - Lin, Justin Yifu, 1994 (Box-folder 30: 5)
  - LIpsky, John, 1997-2003 (Box-folder 30: 6)
  - Loeffler, Axel, 2012 (Box-folder 30: 7)
  - Lombardo, Davide, 2001 May (Box-folder 30: 8)
  - Lu, Shu-shiaun, 2001 (Box-folder 30: 9)
  - Lumsden, Keith, 1985 (Box-folder 30: 10)
  - Machlup, Fritz
    - 1968-1971 (Box-folder 30: 11)
    - 1972-1973 (Box-folder 30: 12)
    - 1976-1982 (Box-folder 1976-1982)
  - MacDonald, Ronald, 1994 (Box-folder 31: 2)
  - Macedo, Jorge Braga de, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 31: 3)
  - Magee, Stephen P., 1973 (Box-folder 31: 4)
  - Makler, Harry M., 2002 (Box-folder 31: 5)
  - Maloney, William F., 1994-1995 (Box-folder 31: 6)
  - Malpass, David, 2010 (Box-folder 31: 7)
  - Mankiw, N. Gregory, 1990 (Box-folder 31: 8)
  - Manova, Kalina, 2009 March 15 (Box-folder 31: 9)
  - Marion, Nancy, 2002 (Box-folder 31: 10)
  - Maskin, Eric S., 1994 March (Box-folder 31: 11)
  - Masson, Paul, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 31: 12)
  - Mathieson, Donald J., 1994 January 11 (Box-folder 31: 13)
  - Mayer, Colin, 1998 April 27 (Box-folder 31: 14)
  - Mayer, Thomas, 1994 September (Box-folder 31: 15)
  - McCauley, Robert N., 1997-1999 (Box-folder 31: 16)
  - McMillan, John, 1996-2004 (Box-folder 32: 1)
  - Meier, G. M., 1994-1995 (Box-folder 32: 2)
  - Melvin, Michael, 1985 February (Box-folder 32: 3)
  - Meese, Richard, 1985 October (Box-folder 32: 4)
  - Meredith, Guy, 1993 June (Box-folder 32: 5)
  - Miles, Marc A., 1976 (Box-folder 32: 6)
  - MItchener, Kris, 2007 April (Box-folder 32: 7)
  - Mohan, Rakesh, 2009 October 22-23 (Box-folder 32: 8)
  - Montinola, Gabriella, 1995 October (Box-folder 32: 9)
  - Moore, Basil, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 32: 10)
  - Morduch, Jonathan, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 32: 11)
  - Murdock, Kevin, 1995 (Box-folder 32: 12)
  - Mussa, Michael L., 1990 December (Box-folder 32: 13)
  - Nair, Amar
    - 2002-2006 (Box-folder 32: 14)
    - 2006 June (Box-folder 32: 15)
  - Nye, John V. C., 2001 April 12 (Box-folder 33: 1)
  - Oates, Wallace E., 1997-2001 (Box-folder 33: 2)
  - Obstfeld
    - 1991-1996 (Box-folder 33: 3)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 33: 4)
    - 2000-2001 (Box-folder 33: 5)
  - Ohno, Kenichi, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 33: 6)
  - Oi, Jean C., 2006 January 29 (Box-folder 33: 7)
  - Orlowski, Lucjan T., 2001 (Box-folder 33: 8)
  - Ortiz Martinez, Guillermo, 2002 (Box-folder 33: 9)
  - Ozden, Çaglar, 2000 (Box-folder 33: 10)
  - Patinkin, Don, 1993 (Box-folder 34: 1)
  - Pei, Chingwin, 1999 December (Box-folder 34: 2)
  - Pei, Minxin, 1995 (Box-folder 34: 3)
  - Pencavel, John, 2013 July 29 (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - Portes, Richard, 1998 (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - Prasad, Eswar, 2006 February 7 (Box-folder 34: 6)
  - Pill, Huw
    - 1997-2001 (Box-folder 34: 7)
    - 2003 (Box-folder 34: 8)
  - Prusa, Thomas J., 1987 (Box-folder 34: 9)
  - Puyana, Alicia, 2004 (Box-folder 34: 10)
  - Qian, Yingyi
    - 1994-1995 (Box-folder 34: 11)
    - 1997-1999 (Box-folder 34: 12)
    - 1999 (Box-folder 34: 13)
  - Qing, Ying, 2006 (Box-folder 34: 14)
  - Quah, Lilian, 2001 March 26 (Box-folder 34: 15)
  - Ray, Edward John, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - Razin, Assaf, 1997 (Box-folder 35: 2)
  - Remolona, Eli M., 1987-1998 (Box-folder 35: 3)
  - Roberts, Molly, 2008 May 2 (Box-folder 35: 4)
  - Roland, Gérard, 1996 April 26-27 (Box-folder 35: 5)
  - Ritter, Thomas, 1998 May 21 (Box-folder 35: 6)
  - Rockoff, Hugh, 1999 (Box-folder 35: 7)
  - Romer, Paul M., 1993 (Box-folder 35: 8)
  - Romer, Thomas, 1991 (Box-folder 35: 9)
  - Rose, Andrew K., 2003-2007 (Box-folder 35: 10)
  - Rozelle, Scott, 1998 (Box-folder 35: 11)
  - Ryan, Michael, 2004 September 29 (Box-folder 35: 12)
  - Sato, Kiyotaka, 1999-2003 (Box-folder 36: 1)
  - Schnabl, Gunther, 2001-2008 (Box-folder 36: 2)
  - Schulze, Günther G., 1995-1997 (Box-folder 36: 3)
  - Schroth, Maximilian, 2008 October 31 (Box-folder 36: 4)
    - 1997-2000 (Box-folder 36: 5)
    - 2002-2005 (Box-folder 36: 6)
  - Sedemund, Jean, 2002 (Box-folder 36: 7)
  - Sethupathy, Prasanna, 2005 (Box-folder 36: 8)
  - Shaw, Anwar, 1995 (Box-folder 36: 9)
  - Shaw, Edward S., 1967-1973 (Box-folder 36: 10)
  - Shoven, John, 2004 May (Box-folder 36: 11)
  - Sialm, Clemens, 1998 March (Box-folder 36: 12)
  - Shen, Minggao, 2001 (Box-folder 36: 13-14)
  - Shin, Jianhuai, 2006 (Box-folder 36: 15)
  - Sinn, Hans-Werner, 1983-1997 (Box-folder 37: 1)
  - Spitzer, Eliot, 2004 March 22 (Box-folder 37: 2)
  - Slavov, Slavi, 2003 (Box-folder 37: 3)
  - Srinivasan, T. N., 1999-2004 (Box-folder 37: 4)
  - Stan, Andrea, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 37: 5)
  - Starrett, David A., 1997 (Box-folder 37: 6)
  - Staiger, Robert W., 1997 (Box-folder 37: 7)
  - Steil, Ben, 2008 (Box-folder 37: 8)
  - Sturzenegger, Federico, 2004 October (Box-folder 37: 9)
  - Svensson, Lars E. O.
    - 1990-1991 (Box-folder 38: 1)
    - 1992-2000 (Box-folder 38: 2)
  - Szapáry, Győrgy, 2000 (Box-folder 38: 3)
  - Tam, Julie K., 2002 January (Box-folder 38: 4)
  - Tam, Kong-Yam
    - 1982-1984 (Box-folder 38: 5)
    - 2004 (Box-folder 38: 6)
  - Tam, On Kit, 1991 (Box-folder 38: 7)
  - Tan, Junyuan Chris, 2002 (Box-folder 38: 8)
  - Taniguchi, Tomohiko, 1993 (Box-folder 38: 9)
  - Tanzi, Vito
    - 1977-1980 (Box-folder 38: 10)
    - 1981-1994 (Box-folder 38: 11)
  - Tavlas, George S.
    - 1993-1997 (Box-folder 38: 12)
    - 1998-2002 (Box-folder 38: 13)
  - Taylor, Alan M., 1998-2002 (Box-folder 39: 1)
  - Taylor, John B.
    - 1992-1995 (Box-folder 39: 2)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 39: 3)
    - 2007-2008 (Box-folder 39: 4)
  - Taylor, M. Scott
    - 1993-1998 (Box-folder 39: 5)
    - 2001-2002 (Box-folder 39: 6)
  - Taylor, Mark P., 2000 November (Box-folder 39: 7)
  - Teh, Robert, 1990 October 18 (Box-folder 39: 8)
  - Thornton, Judith, 1991 (Box-folder 39: 9)
  - Thornton, Julia, 2004 (Box-folder 39: 10)
  - Tobin, James, 1963-1987 (Box-folder 40: 1)
  - Todo, Yasuyuki, 1997, September 30 (Box-folder 40: 2)
  - Tornell, Aaron, 1999 November (Box-folder 40: 3)
  - Tullio, Giuseppe, 1988-1998 (Box-folder 40: 4)
  - Turner, Brandon, 2004 May 20 (Box-folder 40: 5)
  - Velasco, Andrés, 2001 May (Box-folder 40: 6)
  - Vermeulen, Philip, 1995 October 24 (Box-folder 40: 7)
  - Volz, Ulrich, 2006 March 10 (Box-folder 40: 8)
  - Wang, Di, 2010 (Box-folder 40: 9)
  - Wang, Yi David
    - 2009-2010 (Box-folder 40: 10)
    - 2011 (Box-folder 40: 11)
  - Weinstein, David E., 2001 September 14 (Box-folder 41: 1)
  - Willet, Thomas D., 2007 September (Box-folder 41: 2)
  - Williamson, John J., 1998-2006 (Box-folder 41: 3)
  - Wincoop, Eric van, 2001 November (Box-folder 41: 4)
  - Wright, Gavin, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 41: 5)
  - Wright, Mark L. J., 2001-2004 (Box-folder 41: 6)
  - Wu, Denming, 2004 November 28 (Box-folder 41: 7)
  - Wu, Hou-Mou, 1999-2003 (Box-folder 41: 8)
  - Yang, Mu, 2001 July (Box-folder 41: 9)
  - Yoshitomi, Masaru, 2000 (Box-folder 41: 10)
  - Yu, Weibin, 2008 August (Box-folder 41: 11)
  - Zhang, Liqing, 2006 May (Box-folder 41: 12)
  - Zhang, Xiaopu, 2002 February (Box-folder 41: 13)
  - Zou, Liang, 1995 (Box-folder 41: 14)
  - Zussman, Asaf
    - 2001-2002 (Box-folder 42: 1)
    - 2002 (Box-folder 2002)
    - 2003 (Box-folder 42: 3)
    - 2006 (Box-folder 42: 4)
- Subject File, 1991-2007
  - China - economic conditions
    - 1994 (Box-folder 42: 5)
    - 2006 (Box-folder 42: 6)
    - 2007 (Box-folder 42: 7-8)
    - 2007 (Box-folder 43: 1)
  - India - economic conditions
    - 1991-1992 (Box-folder 43: 2)
    - 1993 (Box-folder 43: 3)
    - 1994 (Box-folder 43: 4)
    - 1995 (Box-folder 43: 5)
  - Japan - economic conditions, 2007 June (Box-folder 43: 6)
  - New Zealand - economic conditions
    - 1990-1993 (Box-folder 43: 7)
    - 1995 (Box-folder 43: 8)
- Printed Matter, 1986-2009
  - Monographs, 1991-2006 (Box-folder 44: 1-3)
  - Pamphlets, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 44: 4-9)
  - Papers and reports, 1993-2009 (Box-folder 44: 5-18)